I'll stand on the edge of the world
我将立于世界边缘
Feel something that can't be ignored
察觉难以忽视之谜
What are we up against?
我们正面对着什么
What are we fighting for?
我们又为何物奋战
It's bigger than us
它宽阔无疆
It's only begun
它于此初降
When dark meets the light,
于光暗交汇之刻
it burns like the sun
它如烈阳般燃烧
It's bigger than us
它宽阔无疆
It's only begun
生长不息
So hold on,
瞧吧
We're lighting up the sky
我们正点亮星空
Hold on
坚持不懈
Right here our worlds collide
于此，我们的世界相撞
You know it's far from done
你心知这远非终局
You hear the battle cry
你听见那不息的战号
Now it's our time
此即我们登台之时
We own the night
今夜由我们主宰
Ashes may dance on the ground
灰烬也许只能在地表沉浮
But gravity can't keep us down
但引力束缚不了我们的脚步
A new awakening, looks like it's up to fate
一次新的觉醒，宛若天命既定
Oh
It's bigger than us, it's only begun
祂宽阔无疆，祂于此初降
When dark meets the light, it burns like the sun
于光暗交汇之际，它如烈阳般燃烧
It's bigger than us, it's only begun
它甚于吾辈，它方获新生
(Only begun)
(它方获新生)
(Ten)
十
(Nine)
九
(Eight)
八
(Seven)
七
(Six)
六
(Ignition)
点火
(Four)
四
(Three)
三
(Two)
二
(One)
一
(Zero)
零
(Lift off)
起飞
There's no turning back
退路已却无暇回首
Tonight we will rise
今夜我们崛起攀顶
The fire that's within,
心中火焰
it never dies
永不熄灭
A change of the tide
时局变幻
You can't run, you can't hide
你无所遁形
There's no turning back
无路可退
So hold on
唯余恒心
We're lighting up the sky
我们正点亮星空
(We're lighting up the sky)
(星空将彻夜无眠)
Hold on
坚定脚步
Right here our worlds collide
于此，彼此的世界交融
Now it's our time
此刻弧光闪烁
We own the night
在我们的夜空中
(We own the night)
(Now it's our time)